<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Pack Documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About the Package
================================
Sonic is an open source network operating system based on Linux that runs on switches from multiple vendors and ASICs.
SONiC offers a full-suite of network functionality, like BGP and RDMA, that has been production-hardened in the data centers of some of the largest cloud service providers.
It offers teams the flexibility to create the network solutions they need while leveraging the collective strength of a large ecosystem and community.


=Setup=
* Supports Windows and UNIX Agent.
* SSH must be enabled on target Sonic Machine.
* The Agent should be able to access the Target Sonic machine.

=Variables=
(none)

=Common Input=
-SSH Host                                      Provide target SSH hostname or IP Address where you want execute the commands E.g. localhost
-SSH Port                                      Provide SSH port number
-Username                                      Provide username E.g automic
-password                                      Provide username E.g automic
-Private key File                              Specify path to the private key file. Required if password is not provided e.g /home/automic/.ssh/id_rsa.ppk
-Passphrase                                    Provide passphrase for the private key. 
-Strict Host Key Check                         If Yes, a strict host key check will be performed.
-Connection TimeOut                            Specify connection timeout . Zero means no timeout.
-Timeout                                       Specify command timeout in seconds. Zero means no timeout.
-Allocate TTy                                  Specify whether if TTY allocation should be done or not.
-Options                                       Run using Sudo password.
-Sudo password                                 The password for the Sudo command

=Actions=
Following actions are supported.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.ADD_MEMBER_PORT_TO_VLAN
* Action Description: This Action will add member port to existing VLAN.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.ADD_VLAN
* Action Description:  This action will Add a VLAN on sonic.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_MEMBER_PORT_FROM_VLAN
* Action Description:  This action will Delete a member port from VLAN on sonic.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_VLAN
* Action Description: This action will Delete a VLAN on sonic.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.RUN_SONIC_COMMAND
* Action Description: This action will execute a command on target sonic system.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.SHOW_INTERFACES
* Action Description: This Action will be used to execute show interfaces command.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.LOAD_CONFIGURATION_FROM_MINIGRAPH_FILE
* Action Description: This action will Load Configuration from a given MiniGraph file.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_SONIC.PUB.ACTION.LOAD_MANAGEMENT_CONFIGURATION
* Action Description: This action will Load Management Configuration from a given file.

]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>